Let's come up with the new thing, let me remove every exclusion before I teach you.
So let's see.
So in this video, we are going to learn also technique that was commonly followed by the
threat tactics.
Adding their malware and the exclusion list in Windows Defender.
So if you feel killing all the services, Windows Defender service, sometimes it will create
a noisy alert in media platforms for the analyst who is working on a back and they can
able to look into that.
So what happening in the back in the machine, so it will create a noisy alert, someone
tries to turn off the different services, killing the different services, okay.
So at that time what you can do, you can add the executable, so your malware in the exclusion
path, okay.
So if you add your malware in the exclusion path, usually the Windows Defender, it will
not scan, it will not scan that path, okay.
So it will be pretty easy to add this, go to the virus threat protection window security
and add our remove defender, okay.
So if you move on to this, here you can see an exclusion button, you can add a file to this,
okay.
So as adding a tedious killer in exclusion, so you can see the tedious killer dot EAC has
been added to add it to its exclusion list, okay.
So as removing this, I don't need tedious killer, so the next video we are going to see
that.
Let me add some other things, the thread we start exe, yeah, process hacker to the exclusion
list.
Yeah.
So this is the way you can add it in the exclusion, so one way, but if you feel you
need to add, you need to add to the command line, so here you can see if you command.
So you can add a complete folder for scanning, first to this scanning, you can add one
file, you can add the extension, so it will not, if you add that exe extension, so it will
not scan any exe based extension, so you can add the process, okay.
So if you execute this command, the raw vehicle or I just given, so here you can find raw
killer has been added from here, just the one thing you need to do, you need to have
the path of the execute double, so which path you are going to exclude, and add empty
preference exclusion path, okay.
So you have to execute in a PowerShell as an administrator mode, so that you can add the
exclusion, hope you enjoyed this video, and we will connect you in the next video, guys.
Bye bye.